Guide to the Stephen Henry Schneider Papers SC1053
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Research and Subject Files, Series 4
  - Proposals
    - DOE pre-application (Root & Schneider), 1992 (Box 201, Folder 40)
    - Avoiding dangerous climate change: communicating climate change impacts and policy options, Nov. 2005 (Box 201, Folder 41)
    - Friends of the Earth: International Litigation project proposal (Box 201, Folder 42)
    - Advanced Water Power Projects: OTEC proposal, 2008 (Box 201, Folder 43)
    - Winslow Foundation grant letter, 2010 (Box 201, Folder 44)
    - NSF grant proposal to "enable of constrain international climate change negotiations", 2009 (Box 201, Folder 45)
    - Plan B: Developing a business strategy for the Bulletin of Atomic Scientists, 2009 (Box 201, Folder 46)
    - Forming Board of Editors for the Journal of Environmental Studies & Sciences, 2009 (Box 201, Folder 47)
    - AGCI proposal to Sloan Foundation, 2003 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - proposals 1-3, 1996-2000 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - proposals 2-3, 3-3 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - BAER proposal (Berkeley), 2001 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Bruno proposal, 1999 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Climax (Lucita) (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - California Climate Change Advisory Committee, 2004 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Center for Environmental Science & Policy (CESP), 2004 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, 2007 (Box 245, Item 9-12)
    - Environmental History project (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Exploratorium (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Global Climate Energy Project (GCEP) (Box 245, Item 15-17)
    - Global Green USA (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Hybrid Vigor Institute, 2001 (Box 245, Item 19-21)
    - IGERT proposal, 2004 (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - IMAX - Wild America proposal, 2004 (Box 245, Folder 23)
    - Interdisciplinary Environmental Research Grant, 2004 (Box 245, Folder 24)
    - Keck proposal, 2004 (Box 245, Folder 25)
    - McDonnell Foundation (Box 245, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous proposals (Box 245, Folder 27)
    - National Geographic Sea Studio - The Living Machine, 2001 (Box 245, Folder 28)
    - PEW Charitable Trust (Box 245, Item 29-32)
    - Public Interest Energy Research (PIER) (Box 245, Item 33-37)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 2003 (Box 245, Folder 38)
    - Sanstad, Howarth, DeCanio, Schneider proposal, 2001 (Box 245, Item 39-42)
  - Topics
    - Risk Papers (1/4), 1980s (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Risk Papers (2/4), 1975 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Risk Papers (3/4) (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Risk Papers (4/4) (Box 167, Folder 15)
    - reprints: post Kyoto, carbon cycle, emissions, etc. (1/4), 1990s (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Post-Kyoto climate change papers (2/4), 1990s (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Emissions, Carbon Cycle Papers (3/4), 1990s (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Carbon Cycle Papers (4/4), 1990s (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Self-Governance and Peer Review, 1999 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Media IIS, early-mid 1990s (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Publications: Reevaluating Vegetation Control of Evaporation by Martin, Philippe, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - NCAR: Recommendations for Computing Resources, 1988 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - John Brockman: Every Schoolboy, Science Masters Series, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Food and Agribusiness Memorandum No. 1-10 - Arthur D. Little, Inc. (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - UCAR Teaching Modules - Cambridge U Press, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Univ. Science Books Teaching Modules, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Pulbications: Strategic Energetiques Biosphere & Societe (SEBES), 1995 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Publications: USDA Productivity of America's Forests and Climate Change, 1995 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Education Guides, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Publications: "Mundance Science" by Kammen & Dave, December 1996 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Publications: Climate Variability, Climate Change and Western Water by Miller, Kathleen, 1997 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - NCAR - changes in policy, program and personnel, 1992-95 (Box 170, Folder 18)
    - Social Indicators for Meetings (Box 170, Folder 19)
    - Physics Today Article - Dan Kammen, 1995 (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Nordhaus 2010 (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Propublica/ Larry Pryor, 2010 (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Univ. of Michigan, 1991-92 (Box 170, Folder 23)
    - NCAR Research toward IPCC, late 1980s (Box 170, Folder 24)
    - Georgescu-Roegen, Nicholas, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Publications: "Central Themes of So. Atlantic Circulation w/ data set -includes diskette-, 1997 (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Minority Report: 104th Congress Energy and Environment Sub Committee, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 27)
    - Publications: "The Bad Earth" by Peter Lindert, 1996 (Box 170, Folder 28)
    - NOAA-14 data, 1994-96 (Box 170, Folder 29)
    - Publications: Consequences, 1994-95 (Box 170, Folder 30)
    - Publications: Lingua Franca file (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 170, Folder 31)
    - Lingua Franca (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 170, Folder 32)
    - Contrarians: Bjorn Lomborg, 1998-2009 (Box 186, Item 1-19)
    - Lindzen, Richard S. - issues, 1976-1993 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Contrarians, 1988-1997 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Address by the Rt Hon Margaret Thatcher, FRS, MD to the 44th Session of the United Nations General Assembly, 1989 Nov 8 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Marshall Institute "Scientific Perspectives on the Greenhouse Problem", 1989 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper/Magazine Contrarians, 1989-1995 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Contrarians (1/2), 1990s (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Contrarians (2/2), 1990s (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Contrarians (1/2), 1990s (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Contrarians (2/2), 1990s (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - John Zillman - Contrarians, 1990-1993 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Informed Citizens for the Environment: proposal, marketing examples - Contrarians, 1991 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Ellen Rice (National Research Council), 1992 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Ellen Rice (National Research Council) - papers to review, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - The greening of Planet Earth - Ontario, Canada, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - SHS: Is the "Scientist-Advocate" an Oxymoron?, 1993 (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - The Climate Time Bomb - Contrarians, 1994 (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Fred Singer - Contrarians, 1994 (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Jeremy Leggett - Climate Change: How bad is it? What is being done? What needs to be done? - Contrarians, 1994 (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - MacDonald, Sobel, et. al - Changing Weather? Facts and Fallacies about Climate Change, 1995 (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - Erlich and Erlich "Atmospheric Fables", 1995 (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - Jesse Ausubel - Can Technology Spare the Earth?, 1995 (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Leonie Haimson, Michael Oppenheimer, David Wilcove - The Way Things Really Are: Debunking Rush Limbaugh on the Environment - Contrarians, 1995 (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Don Weaver - Contrarians, 1997 (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - Tom McIver - Ever Since Genesis: Creationism Origins, Evolution and Diversity, 1997 (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - Countering the Sceptics - a rebuttal of sceptics' science - Contrarians, 1998 (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - Contrarians (1/4), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Contrarians (2/4), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Contrarians (3/4), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Contrarians (4/4), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Contrarians (1/2), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Contrarians (2/2), 2000s (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - SCI Data "Contrarians", 2000 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Contrarians, 2000-2002 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Contrarians, 2001 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - The Day After Tomorrow [screenplay] - Contrarians, 2002 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Eileen Crist "Quantifying the Biodiversity Crisis" - Wild Earth, 2002 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Contrarians, 2002-2003 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Malcolm Mann, Raymond Bradley, Malcolm Hughes (aka "MBH) (1/2), 2004 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Malcolm Mann, Raymond Bradley, Malcolm Hughes (aka "MBH) (2/2), 2004 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Imhofe, Jeffords, Soon, Baliunas, Legates - Contrarian, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - "Hockey Stick" Issues - Contrarians, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Michael Crichton Caltech Lecture - Contrarians, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - McIntyre and McKitrick - Corrections to the Mann et al Proxy Data Base and Northern Hemispheric Average Temperature Series, 2004 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - James Imhofe - Hot and Cold Spin Cycle: A challenge to journalists who cover global warming - Contrarians, 2006 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Contrarian, 2005 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - The Great Global Warming Swindle Programme - Australia, 2007 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Edmond Mathez - Climate Change: The Science of Global Warming and Our Energy Future - Contrarians, 2008 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Interview with Felicia Biberica - Contrarians, 2008 (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Carnegie Mellon Integrated Climate Assessment, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Carnegie Mellon Interview, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - CNIE (National Institute for the Environment) (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - British Coal, 1993 January (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Energy (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Energy Efficiency Consulting, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Education, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Coyote Point Museum, 1991 (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Climate Change, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Climate Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Funding Opportunities, 1992-1994 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Future Quest, 1994 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Global Change Forcing, 1980 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Global Systems Science, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - MacArthur, 1994 (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Oxford University Press, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 16)
    - PMIP (Paleoclimatic Modeling Intercomparison Project), 1994 (Box 206, Folder 17)
    - University Programs (UCSB) (Box 206, Folder 18)
    - Universities Space Research Association (Box 206, Folder 19)
    - Paleo Newsletter, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 20)
    - PEW/ Local, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 21)
    - Press: Environment, 1993 (Box 206, Folder 22)
    - Remote Sensing, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 23)
    - UN/ Wider, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 24)
    - DOE Summary of Thrusts, 1995-1996 (Box 206, Folder 25)
    - National 4-H Council, 1997 (Box 206, Folder 26)
    - Weyant Paper (Box 206, Folder 27)
    - Contrarians (1/2), 2003 (Box 206, Folder 28)
    - Contrarians (2/2), 2003 (Box 206, Folder 29)
    - Contrarians (Box 206, Folder 30)
    - Contrarians "Nature, not human activity, rules the climate", 2008 (Box 206, Folder 31)
    - Nut File, 1999 (Box 206, Folder 32)
    - Illustrative Materials for Presentation to: Dept of Interior and Western Governors' Drought Mtg, 1977 Feb 20 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - No Sweat News, 1994-1996 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Drought, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Race to Save the Planet, 1990 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Race to Save the Planet, 1990 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Race to Save the Planet, 1991 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - The Future of Risk, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - SSRC Committee for Research on Global Change, 1993 Oct 7-8 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - SSRC Committee for Research on Global Change, 1993 May 3-4 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - SSRC Committee for Research on Global Change, 1993 May 3-4 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - SSRC Committee for Research on Global Change, 1993 October 3-4 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Aspen Institute Seminar Readings: 21st Century Leaders Program (1/3), 1991 June 28-July 1 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Aspen Institute Seminar Readings: 21st Century Leaders Program (2/3), 1991 June 28-July 1 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Aspen Institute Seminar Readings: 21st Century Leaders Program (3/3), 1991 June 28-July 1 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Earth and Environmental Sciences Directorate (Scientific Advisory Committee Review), 1999 May 25-26 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Forest Workshop, 1993 (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - CO2 scaling problem research (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Extinctions/catastrophes (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Kukla research (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Kutzbach research (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Marine biology: sea levels & oceanography (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Phillipe: research (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell aerosol model (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Money sources (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Natural Systems Group (NSG) (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - NOAA correspondence (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Schneider: copies of writings/letters to ed., etc. (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Schneider, Dickinson & Geisler (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Schneider, Thompson: dust aerosol research (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Schneider, Thompson: research on precipitation rates, 1977 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Schneider, Thompson: Parameterization of Zonal Precipitation rates, 1978 (Box 211, Item 15-16)
    - Sleeper (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - Slides (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Soil management (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - Solar (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Sustainable development (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - Trace Gas effects (Box 211, Folder 22)
    - Tropical Cyclones (Box 211, Folder 23)
    - Tropical Forests (Box 211, Folder 24)
    - Uncertainty (Box 211, Folder 25)
    - Variablity (Box 211, Folder 26)
    - Volcanoes (Box 211, Folder 27)
    - Weather/Meteorological Attractors (Box 211, Folder 28)
    - Wind (Box 211, Folder 29)
    - Younger Dryas research (Box 211, Item 30-31)
    - Ozone depletion (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Paleoclimatic (Box 220, Item 2-4)
    - Policy (Box 220, Item 5-10)
    - Poles/Ice/Glaciers (Box 220, Item 11-12)
    - Philosophy (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - Pollution (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Politics/International conflict/Nuclear weapons (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - Population (Box 220, Item 16-17)
    - Public Health (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - Recycling (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - Risk assesment (Box 220, Folder 20)
    - Bush and the environment (Box 221, Item 1-3)
    - Newsletters:various organizations (Box 221, Item 4-8)
    - Newsletter: Institute on Global Conflict & Cooperation (IGCC) (Box 221, Item 9-10)
    - NCAR media (Box 221, Item 11-17)
    - Economics, 1992-1997 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Education, 1990-1993 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Endangered / Extinction, 1996 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Energy (1/2) (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Energy (2/2) (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Paul and Anne Ehrlich, circa 1997 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - El Nino Reprints, 1987-1994 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Evolution and the Fossil Record, 1976-1990 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Fire, circa 1986 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Food and Agriculture, 1993 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - Forests and Climate Change (1/2), 1991-1996 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Forests and Climate Change (2/2), 1991-1996 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - Forests Climate Signals, 1994-1996 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - Forests and Paleo Climate, 1987-1993 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - Forest Structure and Vegetation, 1984-1995 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - Fresh Water, 1993-1996 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - Gaia, 1987-1990 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - Gender / Hormones, 1994 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - Topics and article reprints in folders labeled "A" through "T". (no folders for letters "C", "I - K", or "Q") (Box 237, Item 1-15)
    - Artic Haze (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Atmosphere (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Authorization (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Biogeochemical cycles (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - CO2 reprints (Box 234, Item 5-6)
    - Climate modeling (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Climate monitoring (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Clouds (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Dark Vision (nuclear winter) (Box 234, Item 10-12)
    - Deforetration (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - Drought (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - Ecology (Box 234, Item 15-16)
    - Economics (Box 234, Item 17-18)
    - NCAR work on the Climate System Modeling Project (CSMP), 1988-1990 (Box 235, Item 1-15)
    - Greenouse Effect and Global Warming, 1995 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Global Climate Change, 1988-1994 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Mammals, 1994 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Integrated Assessment, 1994-1996 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Land Use / Land Cover, 1992-1994 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Greenhouse Dissenters, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Greenhouse Effect and Global Warming, circa 1989 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Nuclear Seasons (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Nuclear Autumn, 1986 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Nordhaus, 1996 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Media, 1990 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Nasty Surprises (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Local Climate Change (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Nuclear Seasons (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Seasons (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Contrarians (additional material) (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Surface Winds, Wind Stress and Weather Over the Tropical Pacific During the FGGE Hawaii to Tahiti Oceanographic Shuttle. Dept. of Meterology, University of Hawaii. [FGGE: First GARP Global Experiment] [GARP: Global Atmospheric Research Program], 1979-1980 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Global Distribution of Total Cloud Cover and Cloud Amounts Over the Ocean. National Center for Atmospheric Research., 1988 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Global Distribution of Total Cloud Cover and Cloud Amounts Over Land. National Center for Atmospheric Research., 1986 (Box 250, Folder 4)
  - Organizations
    - Aldo Leopold Leadership Program (Box 202, Item 1-2)
    - AMS, 2006-2007 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - American for a Sustainable Economy (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Aspen Global Change Institute (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Atmospheric Science Library (Kluwer) (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Blue Planet Prize (nominator) (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Bren advisory Board, 2004 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Project 3650 Advisory board, May 2006 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - California Climate Change Advisory committee, 2003 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - California Wild (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - California Guide for Environmental Literacy (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Carnegie Mellon (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Center for a Sustainable Economy (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - James Martin Institute - Oxford Univ., 2004 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Civil & Environmental Engineering REES search committee, 2004 (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Climate Institute - faculty club lunch with John Topping, May 10, 1995 (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Climate Institute (Box 202, Item 18-22)
    - Climate Institute - Climate Alert Newsletter (Box 202, Item 23)
    - Columbia University (Box 202, Item 24)
    - Consequences editorial board (Box 202, Item 25)
    - Conservation Biology editorial board (Box 202, Item 26)
    - Conservation International (Box 202, Item 27)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 202, Item 28)
    - Governor Davis's bill, 2002 (Box 202, Item 29)
    - Climate Policy (Box 202, Item 30)
    - Earth Communications Office, 1989-1991 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Earth and Sky Science Advisor, 2000-2002 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Earth Day National Council, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Earth Systems, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Earth Systems, 1996 March 18 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Earth Systems Science, 1991-2000 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Earth and Environmental Science Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Ecofables / Ecosciences, 1997 July 14 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Ecological Economics Editorial Board, 1998-1999 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Ecological Society of America - Spring Green Project, 1994 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Ecological Society of America and Union of Concerned Scientists Project, 1997-1998 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Encyclopedia Americana Editorial Board, 1995 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (EDF), 1999-2000 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Eco Health Manuscripts, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Learning Fund, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Media Association - Board Meetings, 1993-1996 (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - Environmental Scientists for Global Survival, 1988-1991 (Box 205, Folder 17)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1988-1993 (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Geophysical Research Letters, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 19)
    - Global Green, 2006 (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - National Advisory Board for Green Leaf Honor Society for ES, 1998 (Box 205, Folder 21)
    - Human Dimensions of Global Change - Navy Symposium, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 22)
    - The Heinz Awards, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 23)
    - International Commission on Climate, 1986-1996 (Box 205, Folder 24)
    - Robert Weisberg, 1994 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Personal Business, 1991-1996 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Airline Perks Correspondence, 1996, 2007 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Travel Perks, Patagonia, Travel Information, 1992-2000 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Airlines A-D, 1994-1997 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Airlines F-Z, 1994-2000 (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - AAAS (Academy Association for the Advancement of Science) - Chair and Membership, 2000-2005 (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - AAAS Proposals, 2000 (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - AAAS Organization, 1993-2000 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - AAAS Climate and Water Panel Committees, 1984-1986, 2000 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - AAAS Committee on Climate, 1987 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - AAAS Committee on Climate, 1984-1991 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - AAAS Member-At-Large Section Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Academia Europa, 1998-2005 (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - AGU Front Range Branch, 1988-1989 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - AMS (S. Manabe), 2005 (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Aspen Global Change Institute (AGCI) - "Science Committee", 2005-2006 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Imagica Science Advisor 2001 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory, 1991-1993 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Lab, 1999-2001 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 2000 (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - MAHB - Enrlich, 2005 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Marquis Who's Who Galley Proof, 2000 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Millenium Ecosystem Assessment, 2001 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Microsoft (Encarta Encyclopedia), 1999 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Mitigatron and Adapt Strategies for Global Change - ED Board, 1993 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - NAS Correspondence, 2002 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - NAS Ballot Confidential, 2006 (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - NAS 140th Annual Meeting - Washington, 2003 April 25-30 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Confidential NAS Ballot, 2006 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 2005 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - National Institute for the Environment, 1990 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - National Environment Education Article Background, 1990-1992 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - National Environment Education Standards Project, 1996 (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Pacific Institute, 1988-1990 (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Palo Alto Bar Association, 1999 June 9 (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Pacific Council on International Policy, 1996-1998 (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - National Wildlife Federation Contributors Agreement, 2001 (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - Analyzing Biospheric Change (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - American Bar Association: Science Advisory Panel (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - American Institute of Physics: Visiting Scientist Program (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - American Museum of Natural History/Environmental Defense Fund (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Arid Ecosystems/UCAR Boulder,CO, October 1989 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Center for Children and Technology (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Center for Environment Information Inc. (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Climate Club (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - Collage-Children's Museum (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Colorado Consortium (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Colorado Journal of International Environmental Law & Policy (Box 219, Folder 11)